<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello Friend</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hello Friend</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m an aspiring full stack developer.
I love traveling, animals, hacking and music. Studied Computer Networking at Federal University of Ceará from 2014 to 2017. Worked at Trixlog from 2017 to 2018. Currently studying the field of Information Security and working as DevOps at Instituto Atlântico.
Main experiences: Python, AWS, Docker, Kubernetes, Prometheus, Terraform.
 Contact: LinkedIn  Github  Telegram  Instagram  Email  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a Virtual Lab with Virtualbox</title>
      <link>/posts/virtualbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/virtualbox/</guid>
      <description>Setting up a Virtual Lab with Virtualbox This documentation shows how to configure an virtual environment for pentesting, researching and experimentation using VirtualBox, a virtualization software that allow us to simulate a real life scenario. We will have the following topology:
Configure the VMs with the following specifications, either by downloading the ISOs or the OVF files.
   Role OS CPU RAM Network Interfaces IP Address User Password     Gateway Ubuntu 18.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/posts/arpspoof/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/arpspoof/</guid>
      <description>ARP Spoofing ARP is a protocol from The TCP/IP model, which stands for Address Resolution Protocol, and the purpose of it is to translate IP address to MAC address and vice versa.
Each host has an ARP table, with the entries of IP/MAC associations from the other known hosts in the localnetwork. to check the ARP table from your host, run:
arp -a  How ARP protocol works:
Client sends and ARP request in broadcast:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>